Guide to the Child Study Center, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Child Study Center, School of Medicine, Yale University, records
1931-2008
RU 910
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
81.35
93 boxes
5363.85
The records consist of correspondence, speeches, presentations, and photographs documenting the tenure of Dr. Donald J. Cohen as director of the Child Study Center at the Yale School of Medicine. Records of Guidance Nursery and School Development Program and records created by Katherine Wolf are also included.
Yale University. Child Study Center
Cohen, Donald J.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 27-E (YRG 27-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Medicine.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Child Study Center, 2002, 2008, 2010; National Library of Medicine, 2008; gift of Janet L. Barney, 2008; gift of Deborah K. Trofatter, 2011.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, speeches, presentations, and photographs documenting the tenure of Dr. Donald J. Cohen as director of the Child Study Center at the Yale School of Medicine. Records of Guidance Nursery and School Development Program and records created by Katherine Wolf are also included.
Child development -- Research; Child development -- Study and teaching; Child psychiatry -- Research; Child psychiatry -- Study and teaching; Child psychology -- Research; Child psychology -- Study and teaching; Yale University. Child Study Center; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Records of Donald J. Cohen as director, 1970-2001; Accession 2002-A-211
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - Articles written by Dr. Cohen
    - Justin and his peers: An experimental analysis of a child's social world. Child Development (Box 1)
    - Catalysis of controlled leadership in cooperation by human stimulation. (Box 1)
    - The crying newborn's accommodation to the nipple. Child Development (Box 1)
    - Personality development in twins: Competence in the newborn and preschool years. (Box 1)
    - The medical care of autistic children. (Box 1)
    - Separating identical from fraternal twins. Archives Of General Psychiatry (Box 1)
    - Companion instruments for measuring children's competence and parental style. Archives Of General Psychiatry (Box 1)
    - Reliably separating identical from fraternal twins. Archives Of General Psychiatry (Box 1)
    - (4 slides 35 mm, two negatives and 5 Graphs in an envelope) (Box 1)
    - Reduced cerebrospinal fluid 5-hydroxyindoleacetic acid and homovanillic acid in children with epilepsy (Box 1)
    - The diagnostic process in child psychiatry. Psychiatric Annals (Box 1)
    - Primary childhood aphasia and childhood autism: Clinical, biological, and conceptual observations (Box 1)
    - Pica And Elevated Blood Lead Level In Autistic And Atypical Children. (Box 1)
    - Creatine Phosphokinase Levels In Children With Severe Developmental Disturbances. Archives Of General Psychiatry (Box 1)
    - Platelet Monoamine Oxidase Activity In. Children And (Box 1)
    - Adolescents. Life Sciences, L8:9l9-924. (1980) (Box 1)
    - Cognitive Structures, Language, And Emerging Social Competence In Autistic And Aphasic Children. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Language Development And Its Disorders: Introduction. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Assessment Of Cerebrospinal Monoamine Metabolites In Children Using The Probenecid Method. The Israel Annals Of Psychiatry And Related Disciplines (1977) (Box 1)
    - Dopamine And Serotonin Metabolism In Neuropsychiatrically Disturbed Children: CSF Homovanillic Acid And 5-Hydroxyindoleacetic Acid. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Fathers' And Mothers' Perceptions Of Children's Personality. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Parental Style: Mothers' And Fathers' Perceptions Of Their Relations With Twin Children. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Platelet Monoamine Oxidase In Early Childhood Autism. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Cardiovascular Correlates Of Attention In Normal And Psychiatrically Disturbed Children: Blood Pressure, Peripheral Blood Flow, And Peripheral Vascular Resistance. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Neurochemistry And Child Psychiatry. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Federal Day Care Standards: Rationale And Recommendations. American Journal Of Orthopsychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Personality Development In Children With Growth Hormone Deficiency. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - CSF Monoamine Metabolites In Children With Minimal Brain Dysfunction: Evidence For Alteration Of Brain Dopamine. Journal Of Pediatrics (1977) (Box 1)
    - Childhood Autism: Cerebrospinal Fluid Examination And Immunoglobulin Levels. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1977) (Box 1)
    - Childhood Autism. Children Today Vol. 4 No. 4 July-August (1975) (Box 1)
    - Animal Models And Childhood Behavioral Disturbances: Dopamine Depletion In The Newborn Rat Pup. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1978) (Box 1)
    - Agreement In Diagnosis: Clinical Assessment And Behavior Rating Scales For Pervasively Disturbed Children. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1978) (Box 1)
    - Chronic, Multiple Tics Of Gilles De La Tourette's Disease: CSF Acid Monoamine Metabolites After Probenecid Administration. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1978) (Box 1)
    - The Biochemical Basis Of Minimal Brain Dysfunction. The Journal Of Pediatrics (1978) (Box 1)
    - EEG Profiles Of Neuropsychiatrically Disturbed Children. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1978) (Box 1)
    - Decreased Urinary Free Catecholamines In Childhood Autism. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1978) (Box 1)
    - Association Between Platelet Monoamine Oxidase Activity And Hematocrit In Childhood Autism. Life Sciences (1978) (Box 1)
    - Central Biogenic Amine Metabolism In Children With The Syndrome Of Chronic Multiple Tics Of Gilles De La Tourette: Norepinephrine, Serotonin, And Dopamine. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1978) (Box 1)
    - Maternal Care Received By Rat Pups Treated With 6-Hydroxydopamine. Physiology And Behavior (1979) (Box 1)
    - Reye Syndrome: Monoamine Metabolites In Ventricular Fluid. Neurology (1979) (Box 1)
    - Decreased 24-Hour Urinary MHPG In Childhood Autism. American Journal Of Psychiatry (1979) (Box 1)
    - Psychological Sequelae Of Relative "Treatment Failure" For Children Receiving Human Growth Hormone Replacement. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1979) (Box 1)
    - Social Interaction And Sensory Intake Rejection: Cardiovascular Correlates Of Attention In Young Adults And School-Aged Boys. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1979) (No Article only some graphs) (Box 1)
    - Psychosocial Concomitants Of Biological Maturation In Preadolescence. American Journal Of Psychiatry (1979) (Box 1)
    - New Diagnostic Terminology For Minimal Brain Dysfunction. Journal Of Pediatrics (1979) (Box 1)
    - Detection Of Phenylketonuria In Autistic And Psychotic Children. Journal Of The American Medical Association (1980) (Box 1)
    - The Effect Of Unfamiliar Tasks And Teachers On Autistic Children's Negativism. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1980) (Box 1)
    - Pathways Between Constitution And Competence During The First 5 Years Of Life. Developmental Psychobiology (1980) (Box 1)
    - Monoamine Oxidase And Catechol-O-Methyltransferase Activities In Cultured Fibroblasts And Blood Cells From Children With Autism And The Gilles De La Tourette Syndrome. Psychiatry Research (1980) (Box 1)
    - Serum Dopamine-Beta-Hydroxylase Activity: Clinical Applications In Child Psychiatry. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1980) (Box 1)
    - Behavior And Learning Difficulties In Children Of Normal Intelligence Born To Alcoholic Mothers. Journal Of Pediatrics (1980) (Box 1)
    - Environmental Influences On Body Weight And Behavior In Developing Rats After Neonatal 6-Hydroxydopamine (1980) (Box 1)
    - Effects Of 6-Hydroxydopamine And Amphetamine On Rat Mothering Behavior And Offspring Development. Pharmacology Biochemistry And Behavior (1980) (Box 1)
    - Amphetamine And Maternal Behavior: Dose Response Relationships. Psychopharmacology (1980) (Box 1)
    - Constructive And Re-Constructive Activities In The Analysis Of A Depressed Child. Psychoanalytic Study Of The Child (1980) (Box 1)
    - Familial Pattern Of Gilles De La Tourette Syndrome. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1980) (Box 1)
    - Clonidine Ameliorates Gilles De La Tourette Syndrome. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1980) (Box 1)
    - Sensory Experiences Of Gilles De La Tourette Syndrome. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1980) (Box 1)
    - Thyroid Hormone In Autistic Children. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1980) (Box 1)
    - Effects Of Continuous Gastric Infusion Of Food Dyes On Developing Rat Pups. Life Sciences (1980) (Box 1)
    - Ontogeny Of Dopamine And Serotonin Metabolites In The Cerebrospinal Fluid Of Children With Neurological Disorders. Developmental Medicine And Child Neurology (1980) (Box 1)
    - Differential Effects Of Maternal And Sibling Presence On Hyperactivity Of 6-Hydroxydopamine-Treated Developing Rats (1981) (Box 1)
    - Sensory Receptor Sensitivity In Autistic Children: Response Times To Proximal And Distal Stimulation. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1981) (Box 1)
    - Folic Acid And B12In Autism And Neuropsychiatric Disturbances Of Childhood. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1981) (Box 1)
    - Computed Tomographic Brain Scanning In Chidren With Developmental Neuropsychiatric Disorders. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1981) (Box 1)
    - Cerebrospinal Fluid, Plasma, And Urinary MHPG In Children. Life Sciences (1981) (Box 1)
    - Plasma Free MHPG And Neuroendocrine Responses To Challenge Doses Of Clonidine In Tourette's Syndrome: Preliminary Report. Life Sciences (1981) (Box 1)
    - Familial Pattern And Transmission Of Gilles De La Tourette Syndrome And Multiple Tics. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1981) (Box 1)
    - Personality Development In Identical Twins: The First Decade Of Life. Psychoanalytic Study Of The Child (1981) (Box 1)
    - School Avoidance And Social Phobia Triggered By Haloperidol In Patients With Tourette's Disorder. American Journal Of Psychiatry (1981) (Box 1)
    - Modulation Of Sensory Intake In Autistic Children: Cardiovascular And Behavioral Indices. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1981) (Box 1)
    - Urinary Free Catecholamines Determined By Liquid Chromatography-Fluorometry. Clinical Chemistry (1981) (Box 1)
    - Effects Of Bromocriptine In Developing Rat Pups After 6-Hydroxydopamine. Pharmacology, Biochemistry And Behavior (1981) (Box 1)
    - Psychopharmacology Of Attention Deficit Disorder: Pharmacokinetic, Neuroendocrine And Behavioral Measures Following Acute And Chronic Treatment With Methylphenidate. Pediatrics (1982) (Box 1)
    - Long-Term Consequences Of Reye Syndrome: A Sibling Matched Controlled Study Of Neurologic, Cognitive, Academic And Psychiatric Function In Reye Syndrome. Journal Of Pediatrics (1982) (Box 1)
    - Stimulant Medications Precipitate Tourette's Syndrome. Journal Of The American Medical Association (1982) (Box 1)
    - A Hierarchial Analysis Of Patterns Of Noncompliance In Autistic And Behavior Disturbed Children. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1982) (Box 1)
    - Modulation Of Response To Environmental Stimulation In Autistic Children. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1982) (Box 1)
    - Blood Lead In Autistic Children. (1982) (Box 1)
    - Environmental And Biologic Interactions On Behavior: Effects Of Artificial Rearing In Rat Pups Treated With 6-Hydroxydopamine. Developmental Psychobiology (1982) (Box 1)
    - Effects Of Apomorphine On Appetitive Conditioning In 6-Hydroxydopamine Treated Rat Pups. Pharmacology, Biochemistry And Behavior (1982) (Box 1)
    - Preface To The Special Issue On Neurobiological Research In Autism. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1982) (Box 1)
    - A Longitudinal Study Of Patients With Severe Developmental Disorders Of Language Learning. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1983) (Box 1)
    - Letter To The Editor: Irritability In Autistic Children Treated With Fenfluramine. New England Journal Of Medicine (1983) (Box 1)
    - Neurochemische Aspecten Van Kinderlijk Autisme. Tijdschrift Voor Psychiatrie (1983) (Box 1)
    - Autistic Behavior In A Boy With Noonan Syndrome: Case Report. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1983) (Box 1)
    - A Comparison Of HPLC, GC-Mass Spectrometric (GC-MS), And Fluorometric Methods For The Determination Of Homovanillic (HVA) And 5-Hydroxyindoleacetic Acid (5-HIAA) In Human CSF. Journal Of Chromatography (1983) (Box 1)
    - Dopaminergic, But Not Noradrenergic Mediation Of Hyperactivity And Performance Deficits In The Developing Rat Pup. Psychopharmacology (1984) (Box 1)
    - EEG Abnormalities In Tourette's Syndrome. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1984) (Box 1)
    - Attention Deficit Disorder: Quantitative Analysis Of CT Neurology (1984) (Box 1)
    - The Risk Of TS/CMT Among Relatives Of TS Patients Obtained By Direct Interview. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry. (1984) (Box 1)
    - Outcomes Of Severe Disorders Of Language Acquisition. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1984) (Box 1)
    - Parotid Salivary Response To Clonidine In Tourette's Syndrome: Indicators Of Noradrenergic Responsivity. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1984) (Box 1)
    - Poor Outcome And Low Platelet Mao Activity In Chronic Schizophrenia. American Journal Of Psychiatry (1984) (Box 1)
    - CSF Neurochemistry Of Women With Anorexia Nervosa And Normal Women. American Journal Of Psychiatry (1984) (Box 1)
    - Tourette's Syndrome: Advances In Treatment And Research. Introduction To Special Section. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1984) (Box 1)
    - Platelet Imipramine Binding In Autistic Subjects. Psychiatry Research (1984) (Box 1)
    - Central Tryptamine Turnover In Depression, Schizophrenia And Anorexia: Measurements Of Indoleacetic Acid In Cerebrospinal Fluid. Biological Psychiatry (1984) (Box 1)
    - Possible Change In Noradrenergic Receptor Sensitivity Following Methylphenidate Treatment: Growth Hormone And MHPG Response To Clonidine Challenge In Children With Attention Deficit Disorder. Life Sciences (1984) (Box 1)
    - Radial Arm Maze Performance In Rats Following Neonatal Dopamine Depletion. Developmental Psychobiology (1984) (Box 1)
    - Responses To Contingent Queries In Adults With Autistic Disorders And Mental Retardation, Applied Psycholinguistics (1984) (Box 1)
    - Depressed Mood During Pregnancy And The Puerperium: Clinical Recognition And Implications For Clinical Practice, American Journal Of Psychiatry (1984) (Box 1)
    - Differential Effects Of Selective Dopamine, Norepinephrine Or Catecholamine Depletion On Activity And Learning In The Developing Rat. Pharmacology Biochemistry And Behavior (1984) (Box 1)
    - Neurochemische Aspecten Van Het Syndroom Van Gilles De La Tourette. Tijschrift Voor Psychiatrie (1985) (Box 1)
    - Clonidine Benefits Children With Attention Deficit Disorder And Hyperactivity: Report Of A Double-Blind Placebo Crossover Therapeutic Trial, Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1985) (Box 1)
    - An Evaluation Of DSM Iii Criteria For Infantile Autism. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (Box 1)
    - A Twin Study Of Tourette Syndrome. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1985) (Box 1)
    - Computed Tomographic Brain Scanning In Four Neuropsychiatric Disorders Of Childhood: Attention Deficit Disorder, Autism, Language Disorder, And Tourette's Disorder, American Journal Of Psychiatry (1985) (Box 1)
    - Comprehension Of Indirect Requests In Adults With Mental Retardation And Pervasive Developmental Disorders, Journal Of Speech And Hearing Research (1985) (Box 1)
    - Components Of Attention, Methylphenidate Dosage And Blood Levels In Children With Attention Deficit Disorder. Pediatrics (1985) (Box 1)
    - Inappropriate Uses Of Stimulant Medications. Clinical Pediatrics (1985) (Box 1)
    - The Effect Of A Meal On Human Whole Blood Serotonin, Gastroenterology (1985) (Box 1)
    - The Experience Of Infantile Autism: A First Person Account By Tony W. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1985) (Box 1)
    - Cerebrospinal Fluid (CSF) And Brain Monoamine Metabolites In The Developing Rat Pup. Developmental Brain Research (1985) (Box 1)
    - Short And Long Term Treatment Of Tourette's Syndrome With Clonidine: A Clinical Perspective. Neurology (1985) (Box 1)
    - Compliance, "Negativism", And The Effects Of Treatment Structure On Behavior In Autism: A Naturalistic, Behavioral Study. Journal Of Child Psychology And Psychiatry (1985) (Box 1)
    - Age Of Recognition Of Pervasive Developmental Disorder. American Journal Of Psychiatry (Box 1)
    - Clonidine (Dixarit) ALS Medicatie Bijhet Syndroom Van Gilles De La Tourette. JDR Journal For Drug Therapy And Research (1985) (Box 1)
    - Brief Report: Snout And Visual Rooting Reflex In Infantile Autism, Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1985) (Box 1)
    - Autonomic Dysfunction, Peripheral Neuropathy And Depression: Clinical And Neurochemical Evidence Of A Defect Involving Both Peripheral And Central Noradrenergic Systems. Pediatric Neurology (1985) (Box 1)
    - Brief Debrisoquin Administration To Assess Central Dopaminergic Function In Children. Life Sciences (1986) (Box 1)
    - Clinical And Multivariate Approaches To Nosology Of Pervasive Developmental Disorders. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1986) (Box 1)
    - Issues In The Classification Of Pervasive And Other Developmental Disorders: Toward DSM-Iv. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1986) (Box 1)
    - Gilles De La Tourette's Syndrome: Tics And Central Nervous System Stimulants In Twins And Non-Twins. Neurology (1986) (Box 1)
    - Gilles De La Tourette's Syndrome And Attention Deficit Disorder With Hyperactivity: Evidence Against A Genetic Relationship. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1986) (Box 1)
    - Assessment Of Central Dopaminergic Function Using Plasma-Free Homovanillic Acid After Debrisoquin Administration. Journal Of Neural Transmission (1986) (Box 1)
    - Current Concepts: Infantile Autism And The Pervasive Developmental Disorders. Journal Of Developmental And Behavioral Pediatrics (1986) (Box 1)
    - Gilles De La Tourette's Syndrome And Obsessive Compulsive Disorder: Evidence Supporting A Genetic Relationship. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1986) (Box 1)
    - Introduction: Issues In The Classification Of Pervasive And Other Developmental Disorders: History And Current Status Of Nosology. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1986) (Box 1)
    - A Comparison Of Language Characteristics Of Mentally Retarded Adults With Fragile-X Syndrome And Those With Nonspecific Mental Retardation And Autism. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1987) (Box 1)
    - Whole Blood Serotonin In Autistic And Normal Subjects. Journal Of Child Psychology and Psychiatry (1987) (Box 1)
    - Parotid Gland Salivary Secretion In Tourette's Syndrome And Attention Deficit Disorder: A Model System For The Study Of Neurochemical Regulation, Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry. (1987) (Box 2)
    - Amphetamine Reverses Learning Deficits In 6- Hydroxydopamine Treated Rat Pups, Developmental Psychobiology (1987) (Box 2)
    - Steady-State Model For Plasma Free And Platelet Serotonin In Man, Life Sciences (1987) (Box 2)
    - Clinical Features Of Autistic Children With Setback Course In Their Infancy. The Japanese Journal Of Psychiatry And Neurology (1987) (Box 2)
    - Urinary 5-Hydroxyindoleacetic Acid And Whole Blood Serotonin And Tryptophan In Autistic And Normal Subjects. Biological Psychiatry (1987) (Box 2)
    - Analytic Discussions With Oedipal Children. Psychoanalytic Study Of The Child (1987) (Box 2)
    - Cerebrospinal Fluid Indoleacetic Acid In Autistic Subjects. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1988) (Box 2)
    - An Evaluation Of The Autism Behavior Checklist. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1988) (Box 2)
    - Phenomenology And Classification Of The Childhood Psychoses. Psychological Medicine (1988) (Box 2)
    - High Performance Liquid Chromatographic Analysis Of Neurotransmitter Amino Acids In Brain. Journal Of Chromatography (1988) (Box 2)
    - The Ontogeny Of 3, 4-Dihydroxyphenylacetic Acid (DOPAC) In Human Cerebrospinal Fluid. Journal Of Neurology, Neurosurgery And Psychiatry (1988) No Article Only correspondence with the Journal. (Box 2)
    - Elevated CSF Dynorphin A [1-8] In Tourette's Syndrome. Life Sciences (1988) (Box 2)
    - Whole Blood Serotonin And Tryptophan In Autism: Temporal Stability And The Effects Of Medication. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1989) (Box 2)
    - Disintegrative Disorder Of "Late Onset" Autism. Journal Of Child Psychology and Psychiatry (Box 2)
    - An Examination Of Social Typologies In Autism. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child And Adolescent Psychiatry (1989) (Box 2)
    - Facial Perception In Autism: An Experimental Study. Journal Of Child Psychology and Psychiatry (1989) (Box 2)
    - Serotonergic Responsivity In Male Young Adults With Autistic Disorder. Archives Of General Psychiatry (1989) (Box 2)
    - The Issue Of Hyperserotonemia And Platelet Serotonin Exposure: A Preliminary Study. Journal Of Autism And Developmental Disorders (1989) (Box 2)
    - Child And Adolescent Psychiatric Disorders In DSM IV: Issues Facing The Child Psychiatry Work Group. Journal Of The American Academy Of Child and Adolescent Psychiatry (1989) (Box 2)
    - Growth Hormone And Prolactin Response To Methylphenidate In Children With Attention Deficit Disorder. Life Sciences (1990) (Box 2)